Hey, Tayen. Um, welcome back. I know at
the end of the year you had talked about
wanting to return, but uh, what
ultimately led you to decide that this
is where you wanted to be?
>> Um, honestly, um, man, it Adam and DQ,
man, they just made it feel like home.
Um, and I couldn't be more happy with
this environment. Um, you know, God put
me here for a reason and last year and I
just felt like, you know, he was calling
me to come back and, you know, I'm a
follower of Christ. So, that's what I
wanted to do. And, you know, uh, I just
enjoyed playing here, being around all
my teammates, the faculty, everybody in
this building is just awesome. And, you
know, I just wanted to keep that thing
rolling.
I know your season was more than that
one catch, but how often in this
offseason have you have people said to
you, "Hey, that was a hell of a catch."
>> Um, a lot. A lot. Um, you know, uh, that
was that was just a, you know, moment,
you know, that God put me in and, you
know, I took advantage of it and, um,
you know, I'm just super blessed for
that.
>> Hey, congrats. Welcome back. Where do
you feel like you were able to most show
in your time here last year?
>> Um, honestly, I feel like just
everywhere, not only on the field, off
the field, just being there for guys.
Um, being there, you know, when
everything's going good or when it's
going bad, just being that same person
and just carrying myself with a
mentality of, you know, get right back
up and keep going. And, you know, that's
just who I am. So,
>> what have you learned throughout what
what did you learn throughout your first
several years in the NFL that it maybe
will help you moving forward and get
maybe find that home that you want?
>> Um, I would just say, um, you know, just
not taking everything for granted. Um,
going about it like a pro. Um, and just,
you know, honoring each and every day,
whether it's practice, meetings, or
game. just honoring honoring it like
it's my last, you know, so you know,
because it could be taken away at any
point. So,
>> Anna,
>> hey Tayen, welcome back again. Uh, you
talked about enjoying last year. What
did you enjoy most about last year as
you grow this year moving forward?
>> Um, I would just say just having fun.
Um, I felt like last year brought the
fun back of playing football back for
me. Um, I enjoyed coming to practice,
coming to meetings, um, going out there
and playing ball with the guys and, you
know, it just made me, you know, rejoice
in, you know, everything that God has
done for me and also just bringing that,
you know, little kid back into me when I
used to play football when I was
younger. So, it's just that's that's
what I would say. It's been the most,
you know, fun part about it.
>> Thanks. And when you dive into looking
at yourself as a receiver, where do you
think you need to grow the most or you
see yourself growing the most coming
into this year?
>> Um, I would just say everywhere. Um, you
know, I just feel like, you know, as a
receiver, as any player in the NFL,
there's room for improvement in each
aspect of your game. And, um, I just say
just keep getting better each day.
>> Thanks. Appreciate it.
>> Yes, ma'am.
>> Andy.
Hey Tayen, welcome back. Good to see
you. Um, so can you share a bit about
what I mean? I know you probably don't
want to, you know, can't go into details
about your specific, you know, free
agency experience, but like just overall
kind of the highs and the lows of going
through free agency like what is this
time period like?
>> Um, I would just say for me, I I tend
to, you know, give all my worry and
doubt to God. Um, I don't I don't let
that burden sit on my shoulder. You
know, I enjoy being with my wife and
kids. Um, but I'll just say the that
process has honestly been fun. Um, just
being able to just be myself and, you
know, see what teams or whatever wanted
me for me for who I am. You know what I
mean? So, I would just say that. Um, but
yeah, I'm the type of person I don't I
don't too much let stuff get in the way
and bother me. Um, I just let God handle
that for me.
>> I thank you. Um, and congratulations
again.
>> Yes, ma'am. Thank you.
>> Anybody else?
All right. Cool. Appreciate it.
>> Thank you.